yesiamcheap.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy | Yes, I Am Cheap

This website displays advertisements from various sources. Please read this privacy policy as it may be updated occasionally with no notice to you.

We do not collect personally identifiable information (data collected with an intention to identify and/or contact a person such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address), except as expressly provided for herein. Personally identifiable information may be collected should a consumer contact the website owner on his/her own initiative or respond to an advertisement, contest, or giveaway and provide such personally identifiable information.

The non-personally identifiable information we collect may include as an example, IP address, browser types, operating systems, domain names, language preference, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online transactions and browsing and search activity.

We may use your non-personally identifiable information for the following general purposes: enhancement of our services; marketing; and to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Yes, I Am Cheap uses cookies to help Yes, I Am Cheap identify and track visitors, their usage of the Yes, I Am Cheap website, and their website access preferences. Yes, I Am Cheap visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Yes, I Am Cheap’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Yes, I Am Cheap’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Yes, I Am Cheap and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy

We do not govern or control the content places on sites to which we may have linked.  Please review the privacy policy of each site that you visit.

Finally, I’m not going to sell your information.  Come on people.  There’s enough SPAM in the world and it’s totally not worth it to me to sell your e-mail addresses.

## I HATE SPAM! YOUR INFO GOES NOWHERE BUT HERE.
